<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="61">
    <author>ParamIT</author>
    <version>22.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Animal Helper</en>
        <nl>Dieren verzorger</nl>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Easily make your animals happy by filling up all their needs (Food, water, straw)
Pending features:
- Fill Foodgroups with the different FillTypes
- User should pay for resources used (food, straw, etc);
- Using seasons repricing for calculating these costs

Changelog:
- v1.1.1.0
-- Training of horses has been added. Horses will be trained when a new day has started. Horses will only be trained if the helper
   has been launched at least once in this game-session (will not be persisted in your save-game).
- v1.1.0.0
-- Reworked scripts to work with MaizePlus mods.
-- Script now loops through available foodGroups and fills them (still room for rework)
        ]]></en>
        <nl><![CDATA[Een verzorger die de verzorging van je dieren eenvoudig(er) maakt door in hun behoeftes (Voedsel, water, stro)
te voorzien.

Nog te bouwen functionaliteiten:
- FoodGroups vullen met de verschillende types voer, ipv de eerste die het script tegenkomt voor deze groep
- Kosten in rekening brengen voor gebruikte materialen
- Deze kosten baseren op season "repricing" mechanisme.

Changelog:
- v1.1.1.0
-- Het trainen van paarden is toegevoegd. Paarden worden getraind zodra een nieuwe dag begonnen is en als de helper tenminste een keer
   eerder is gestart (in deze spel-sessie).

- v1.1.0.0
-- Scripts opnieuw gebouwd tbv compatibiliteit met MaizePlus
-- Script loopt nu door beschikbare FoodGroups en vult deze, ipv vastgestelde fillTypes.
]]></nl>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>happyAnimals.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="false"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="animalHelper.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n>
		<text name ="input_ANIMAL_HELPER_HIRE_HELPER">
            <nl>Huur dierenverzorger in</nl>
			<en>Hire animal helper</en>
		</text>
        <text name="ANIMAL_HELPER_UNREGISTERED"><en>AnimalHelper unregistered its eventlisteners.</en></text>
        <text name="ANIMAL_HELPER_STARTED"><en>Hired Animal Helpers are starting their work.</en></text>
        <text name="ANIMAL_HELPER_DONE"><en>Hired Animal Helpers are done. All animals are taken care off</en></text>
	</l10n>
    <actions>
        <action name="ANIMAL_HELPER_HIRE_HELPER" category="ONFOOT" locked="false" ignoreComboMask="false" />
    </actions>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="ANIMAL_HELPER_HIRE_HELPER" >
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_lctrl KEY_9" />
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT"  input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_1" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
    </actions>
</modDesc>